Wouter

Meijer

 $houterm@gmail.com \,|\, 06\text{-}81150561 \,|\, Delft \\ Iinkedin.com/in/wouterjmeijer$

portfolio: hOuter.github.io

Summary

Working a business role at a scale-up allowed me to get hands-on experience with marketing, client-facing communications, stakeholder awareness and sales. These skills are complementary to my interdisciplinary engineering competencies as listed below. My academic interests are with the cognitive aspects of robotics.

Education

Delft University of Technology - MSc. Cognitive Robotics

2019 - Present

Experience with: Machine & Deep Learning, Optimisation, Motion Planning, Machine Perception, Data Analysis & Visualisation, Signal Processing, System Identification, Filtering, Dynamics, Intelligent Vehicles, Man-Machine Interaction, Control, Neuromechanics.

Delft University of Technology - BSc. Mechanical Engineering

2014 - 2019

Minor in Electrical & Biomedical Engineering

Bachelor Thesis @ Systems & Control: "Robot Localization based on collisions and IMU"

Stedelijk Gymnasium Haarlem - VWO NT/NG

2014

Experience

Skelex - Business Development

September 2018 - 2020, Rotterdam

I represented Skelex at numerous events and advised businesses on adopting exoskeleton technology in their workforce. Additionally I set up and orchestrated a campaign to raise exoskeleton awareness and find new customers in the Shipbuilding Sector. I supervised 3 groups of marketing students to execute this campaign.

Freelance - Developer

June 2018 - present, Delft

One project involved building a web calculator to calculate the ROI for refitting light sources with LED's in office buildings. This project was commissioned by a large light source manufacturer.

Mechnificent - Treasurer

March 2016 - Mar 2017, Delft

With a team of 6 Mechanical Engineering students orchestrate the logistics, location, safety and organisation of a party for 1250 students.

Skills

English

French, German, Spanish

Solidworks/CAD

Coding

Cambridge Advanced English

Basic

Mechanical Design - Associate level

Python (num.py, tf, plot.ly, pandas, pyTorch, Keras, scipy, gym)

C++ (ROS, OpenCV, pcl)

. (1105, Opene

Matlab

JavaScript (bootstrap)